Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- The College de la Sainte Famille building. 18 x 24 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref148)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Father Minoli, the school director, working in his office. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1940-1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref149)
  Photographic Prints; Furnishings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Schools/Education; Offices; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen
- Class portrait. 17.8 x 24 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref150)
  Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Medals/Insignia
- Group portrait of the school band with teachers. 11.5 x 17.2 cm, Circa 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref151)
  Students; Group Portraits; Orchestra; Musical Instruments; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Woodwind Instruments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Musicians; Brass Instruments; Children; Men; Boys; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of men in military uniforms. 11.7 x 17.7 cm, Circa 1900 (Object AD_MC_028_ref152)
  Hats; Schools/Education; Military/Soldiers; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Men; Medals/Insignia
- The church of Sainte Famille in Helwan. 11.7 x 17.9 cm, Circa 1900 (Object AD_MC_028_ref153)
  Buildings; Religious Sites; Churches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Streets/Roads
- Group portrait of the school orchestra. 12.3 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref154)
  Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Students; Boys; Musical Instruments; Orchestra; Hats; Teachers; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Woodwind Instruments; Schools/Education; Children; Religious Crosses; Brass Instruments; Uniforms; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of the school orchestra. 11.3 x 18 cm, Circa 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref155)
  Orchestra; Children; Musical Instruments; Brass Instruments; Uniforms; Hats; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Teachers; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students wearing theatrical costumes. 11.7 x 18 cm, Circa 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref156)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Performance Plays; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Students; Group Portraits; Theater; Actors; Costumes; Boys; Painted Backdrops; Schools/Education
- Street view of the Tewfiq Mosque secondary school in Helwan. 24.3 x 18 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref157)
  Streets/Roads; Schools/Education; Religious Sites; Mosques; Arabic Writing; Children; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Street Lamps; Group Portraits; Boys; Palm Trees
- Portrait of Mr. Laurella. 19.3 x 13.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref158)
  Bow Ties; Facial Hair; Albumen Prints; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Men; Photographic Prints; Carte de Visite/Cabinet Card; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits
- Class portrait. 13.9 x 19.2 cm, 1960-1961 (Object AD_MC_028_ref159)
  Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Boys; Photographic Prints; Children
- Group portrait of the sports team. 18.1 x 23.9 cm, 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref160)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Boys; Sports; Football; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Children
- Group portrait of the workers of the school theater with Father Lafrauchi and Father Boromi. 17.2 x 23. 3cm, 1937 (Object AD_MC_028_ref161)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Hats; Costumes; Theater; Gelatin Silver Prints; Workers; Men; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Facial Hair; Children
- Group portrait of students with Father Lighuoretti on a beach in Suez. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1948 (Object AD_MC_028_ref162)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Beaches; Students; Teachers; Seas; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Suez, Egypt; Red Sea; Boys; Umbrellas/Parasols; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Children; Priests/Clergymen
- Students playing football on a field. 15.6 x 24 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref163)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Football; Sports; Boys; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits
- Group portrait of teachers taken during an excursion to the Petrified Forest. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1932 (Object AD_MC_028_ref164)
  Hats; Men; Deserts; Landscapes; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Crosses; Teachers; Cameras; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of students and teachers during a field trip to the Japanese Gardens. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref165)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Gardens; Ponds; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Water; Group Portraits; Students; Teachers; Boys; Men
- Class portrait. 17.1 x 23. 5 cm, 1957-1958 (Object AD_MC_028_ref166)
  Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Men
- View of the Church of the Holy Family. 22.9 x 16.4 cm, Circa 1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref167)
  Buildings; Religious Crosses; Religious Sites; Churches; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Building of the school theater in Helwan. 17.3 x 24 cm, 1937 (Object AD_MC_028_ref168)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Theater; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt
- Elevated street view of a school (from Roston Street No. 28). 18 x 24.1 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref169)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt
- Street view of 'Casa Bugeya' in the Suez Canal previously known as the 'Chelsea Pension'. 16.3 x 23.7 cm, April 26th 1946 (Object AD_MC_028_ref170)
  Buildings; Hotels; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Men; Group Portraits; Palm Trees
- The Helwan Observatory building. 16.6 x 23.9 cm, 1903 (Object AD_MC_028_ref171)
  Observatories; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Telescope; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Buildings
- Class portrait. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref172)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Italian Writing; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Children
- Group portrait of students climbing a rock during a field trip. 9.4 x 14.4 cm, 1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref173)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Men; Teachers; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of students with teachers during a visit to Suez. 9.3 x 14.5 cm, 1955 (Object AD_MC_028_ref174)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Group Portraits; Suez, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Priests/Clergymen; Fountains; Men; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Street view of 'Evergreen' hotel. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref175)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Hotels; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait of men in the gardens of the sulfurous bathhouse in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1888 (Object AD_MC_028_ref176)
  Public Baths; Springs; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors
- Class portrait. 14.5 x 19.4 cm, 1961-1962 (Object AD_MC_028_ref177)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Facial Hair
- Street view of Tawfiq Mosque in Helwan (finished in 1884). 17.7 x 12.6 cm, Circa 1900 (Object AD_MC_028_ref178)
  Religious Sites; Mosques; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt
- The school refectory with a fully prepared dining table. 17.8 x 23.6 cm, Circa 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref179)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Schools/Education; Furnishings
- Two students at the beach during a field trip to Suez. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1946 (Object AD_MC_028_ref180)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Red Sea; Group Portraits; Beaches; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Boys; Students; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; English Writing
- Students in during a field trip to Ain Helwan (Capritage) springs with Father Puppi. 24 x 18 cm, Circa 1950-1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref181)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Springs; Public Baths; Children; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- First 'Capritage' swimming pond in Helwan. 15.5 x 24 cm, Circa 1947 (Object AD_MC_028_ref182)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Ponds; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Public Baths; Springs; Swimming Pools; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees
- Street view of 'Des Princes' hotel at 16 Ibrahim Street. 16.5 x 24 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref183)
  Arabic Writing; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Hotels; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Street Lamps
- Group portrait of students on the bridge in the Japanese Gardens in Helwan. 17.8 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref184)
  Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Bridges; Water; Ponds; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Students; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gardens; Children
- Entrance to the College de la Sainte Famille with Father Francerehi standing at the gates. 18 x 24 cm, Circa 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref185)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Schools/Education; Architecture
- The funeral procession of Father Carimuro Giacomelli on Mansur Street, Helwan. 16.6 x 23.9 cm, November 1924 (Object AD_MC_028_ref186)
  Animals; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Coffins/Caskets; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Horses; Carriages/Coaches; Funeral Proceedings; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Transportation; Group Portraits
- Class portrait of students with two teachers. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, 1958-1959 (Object AD_MC_028_ref187)
  Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Men
- Students playing football in the school playground. 17.8 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref188)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Sports; Students; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Football; Children; Group Portraits; Boys
- Students dancing in the school playground. 16.7 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref189)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Football; Dancing; Nuns; Girls; Women; Group Portraits; Boys
- Student Mario Abdel Galil receiving a medal from Father Vantini during the graduation ceremony. 17.7 x 24 cm, Circa 1953 (Object AD_MC_028_ref190)
  Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Women; Men; Religious Crosses; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Nuns; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Graduation Ceremony; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Awards; Facial Hair; Audiences/Spectators; Boys; Children
- Father posing with students and workers in a group portrait during a field trip. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1936-1937 (Object AD_MC_028_ref191)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Crosses; Hats; Students; Workers; Boys; Men; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students on a camel during a field trip to Giza. 18 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref192)
  Students; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Animals; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Group Portraits; Camels; Schools/Education; Children
- Entrance to Tawfiq Mosque in Helwan. 24 x 17.9 cm, 1884 (Object AD_MC_028_ref193)
  Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Mosques; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites
- Sulfur Spring in Helwan. 24 x 18.1 cm, 1884 (Object AD_MC_028_ref194)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Springs; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Public Baths; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of students on 26 Sharif Street in Helwan at the entrance to the College de la Sainte Famille. 16.1 x 23.8 cm, 1941-1942 (Object AD_MC_028_ref195)
  Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Buildings; Architecture; Children
- Villa balconies on Latif Street in Helwan. 24 x 18 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref196)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Houses
- Group portrait of students with a teacher at the top of a rock during a field trip to the desert. 23.9 x 18 cm, 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref197)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Hats; Deserts; Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Statues of Buddha by the water in the Japanese Gardens in Helwan. 18 x 24.2 cm, 1983 (Object AD_MC_028_ref198)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Ponds; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Outdoors; Statues/Sculptures; Water; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Bridges; Landscapes; Palm Trees
- Class portrait. 17.4 x 23.8 cm, 1959-1960 (Object AD_MC_028_ref199)
  Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- Group outdoor portrait of five teachers. 30.4 x 20.9 cm, 1936 (Object AD_MC_028_ref200)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Facial Hair
- Street view of Helwan. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, May 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref201)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Street Lamps
- Front view of Orthodox Cemetery. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref202)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Orthodox Christianity; Cemeteries; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Crosses; Religious Sites
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref203)
  Men; Water; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Ponds; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Landscapes
- A clergyman (Fr. Varotto) and a boy standing in water in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref204)
  Water; Children; Men; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Boys; Facial Hair
- Group of students sitting on top of a bridge during field trip. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref205)
  Bridges; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Railways; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Boys; Transportation; Group Portraits; Schools/Education
- Four teachers at a table with a microphone. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1965-1966 (Object AD_MC_028_ref206)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Microphones; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of boys school football team., 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref207)
  Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Group Portraits; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Football; Italian Writing; Children
- A group of teachers and officials with trophies during school event. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref208)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Ceremonies; Officials; Men; Group Portraits; Women; Schools/Education; Awards
- Students at the Suez summerhouse. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref209)
  Hats; Suez, Egypt; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Boys; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints
- A portrait of a man sitting with a cane. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref210)
  Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
- Al-Aryan Christian monastery. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref211)
  Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Monasteries/Convents; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Churches; Orthodox Christianity; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites
- A group portrait of schoolboys with a donkey. 9 x 11.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref212)
  Uniforms; Hats; Group Portraits; Boys; Animals; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Donkeys; Schools/Education; Children
- Farmers with a cow-driven plow. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref213)
  Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Workers; Streets/Roads; Machines
- Portrait of boys with their teacher at the Japanese Gardens during a school trip. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref214)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Boys; Uniforms; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair; Men; Gardens; Parks; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Students fishing for crabs in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref215)
  Fish; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Group Portraits; Fishing; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Swimming; Teachers; Suez, Egypt; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Children
- General Mohammed Naguib, first President of the Republic of Egypt, handing out medals and trophies. 9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1952-1954 (Object AD_MC_028_ref216)
  Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Military/Soldiers; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Men; Weapons; English Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Medals/Insignia; Government; Political Leadership; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Officials; Ceremonies; Guns; Awards; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia; Facial Hair; Crowds; Microphones; Naguib, Mohamed Naguib (Mohamed Bey Naguib Youssef Qutb El-Qashlan), 1901-1984
- An official shaking a student's hand at a ceremony. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref217)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Boys; Uniforms; Women; Men; Officials; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Awards; Medals/Insignia; Children; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Medals/Insignia
- Schoolboys drinking water from a drinking fountain. 13.9 x 9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref218)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Fountains; Drinks/Beverages; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children
- Boys swimming in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref219)
  Suez, Egypt; Swimming; Group Portraits; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Red Sea; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Seas; Children
- Men and a woman sitting with a clergyman at a table. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref220)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; English Writing; Hats; Priests/Clergymen; Women; Men; Facial Hair
- A school portrait of schoolboys with their teacher and two clergymen. 9 x 13.2 cm, 1959-1960 (Object AD_MC_028_ref221)
  Italian Writing; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Boys; Men; Children
- Students on a field trip with their teacher. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref222)
  Teachers; Deserts; Boys; Animals; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Shepherds; Sheep; Landscapes; Children; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Mountains/Hills; Men
- A group of schoolboys with their teacher. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref223)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Men
- Boys with their two teachers. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1965-1966 (Object AD_MC_028_ref224)
  Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Schools/Education; Teachers; Group Portraits; Children; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Men
- Boys picking out crops during a field trip. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref225)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Students; Teachers; Uniforms; Boys; Agriculture/Farms; Group Portraits; Children; Schools/Education
- A portrait of an elderly man. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1983 (Object AD_MC_028_ref226)